{
    "subject": "resource/FEAT_(album)",
    "predicate": "property/note",
    "object": "featuring The Rosebuds and Astronautalis",
    "human_readable": "The note about FEAT (album) is that it features The Rosebuds and Astronautalis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9643194079399109,
            "question": "What is the name of the album that features The Rosebuds and Astronautalis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9075669050216675,
            "question": "Does Astronautalis appear on the album FEAT?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9001619219779968,
            "question": "Is The Rosebuds a band featured on the album FEAT?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8911879658699036,
            "question": "What album features musical collaborations with The Rosebuds and Astronautalis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7810666561126709,
            "question": "Besides FEAT, what other albums might feature The Rosebuds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7603527903556824,
            "question": "Which bands feature on the album FEAT?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6164978742599487,
            "question": "Name two artists that appear on the album FEAT."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5740429759025574,
            "question": "What kind of music does Astronautalis typically perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5470659136772156,
            "question": "Who are some of the artists on the album FEAT?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33999142050743103,
            "question": "List the musical acts that contribute to the album FEAT."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The note about FEAT (album) is that it features The Rosebuds and Astronautalis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2059_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of the artists on the album FEAT?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2059_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music does Astronautalis typically perform?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2059_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name two artists that appear on the album FEAT.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2059_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2059_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2059_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2059_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2059_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2059_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2059_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2059_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2059_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2059_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2059_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the triple, as they mention The Rosebuds and Astronautalis in the context of FEAT (album), specifically in songs like \"Our Finest China\" and in a note about the album's features."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information clearly states under the document with file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2059/re-ranker-msmarco/67.txt that \"Our Finest China,\" a song which features The Rosebuds and Astronautalis, is especially easy on the ears. This supports the given note about the FEAT album featuring both The Rosebuds and Astronautalis."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}